hotbuzz4u.com 2013-05-06

# Privacy Policy | Hot Buzz 4U

**Privacy Policy of Hotbuzz4u.com**

This website uses third-party advertising companies (including Google Adsense, Google Affiliate, Infolinks and CJ) to serve ads. These third parties may collect and use information (but not your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, you can visit the advertising companies’ Advertising and Privacy page.

And I respect your privacy very much. I am committed to safeguarding your privacy while online at this site. The following will show you how I gather and disseminate information for this site.

**Cookies  
**A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user’s computer tied to information about the user. This site doesn’t use any cookies. However, some of my business partners use cookies on this site (for example – advertisers). I can’t access or control these cookies once the advertisers have set them.

**Links  
**This site contains many links to other sites because it provides the coupon links for you. Please be aware that I am not responsible for the privacy practices of these other sites. I suggest you to be aware of this when you leave this site,  read the privacy statements of each and every site that collects personally identifiable information.

**Advertisers  
**I use outside ad companies to display ads. These ads may contain cookies and are collected by the advertising companies and I do not have access to this information. I work with the following advertising companies: Commission Junction, Google Adsense, Google Affiliate, Infolinks. Please check the advertisers websites for respective privacy policies.

Commission Junction’s Privacy Policy: <http://www.cj.com/privacy.html>

Google Adsense & Google Affiliate’s Privacy Policy:

[http://www.google.com/support/adsense/bin/answer.py?hl=en&answer=100557](http://www.google.com/support/adsense/bin/answer.py?hl=en&answer=100557)

Infolinks’ Privacy Policy: <http://www.infolinks.com/infolinks-privacy-policy>

**Contact Information  
**If you have any questions about us, please contact **erichiller2009#gmail.com** ( **change # into @).** This privacy policy updated May 2010.
